Total Experience: 11 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science and

Notice Period: 2 Months

Engineering]

Sudeshna Das (1) Featured

Associate Salesforce Certified seeking roles in Salesforce Development, Salesforce Support, Requirement Analysis, Apex Class, Visualforce, Batch Apex, Apex Trigger, Apex Test Class, C#, jQuery, Salesforce.com CRM, ASP. Net, HTML, JavaScript, SOQL, SQL Server



Current Location: Kolkata

Pref. Location: Anywhere in North India, Anywhere in South

India, Anywhere in East India

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Associate, Tech Lead, Salesforce Development, Salesforce Support, Requirement Analysis, Apex Class, Visualforce, Batch Apex, Apex Trigger, Apex Test Class, C#, ¡Query, Salesforce.com CRM, ASP.

Net, HTML, JavaScript, SOQL, SQL Server, Visual Studio

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

Overall 10+yrs of experience in IT which involves application software development, enhancement, support of various kinds of on-premise and cloud-based application.

1+ years of relevant experience with supporting Salesforce in an Enterprise environment.

Hands on experience in development using Apex class, Visualforce, Batch Apex, Apex Trigger, Apex Test Class.

Having good working knowledge with Apex Data loader, Workbench to retrieve and update bulk data.

Experience on customizing standard objects Accounts, Contacts, Opportunities, Products, Cases, Activities and Assets. Involved in various stages of software development lifecycle like requirement analysis, planning, design, build, testing,

debugging, issue solving.

Experienced in solving production ticket as per the business user requirement according to process of application within the predefined SLA.

Work Experience

Cognizant Technology Solution as Associate -Salesforce CRM Mar 2018 to Mar 2019

Ericsson India Global Services Pvt. Ltd as Solution Integrator Jul 2013 to Jul 2017

Elogix Software Pvt. Ltd as Software Developer Jun 2011 to Jun 2013

Development of .net based application

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from West Bengal University of Technology (WBUT) in 2006

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C#, Jquery		2017	9 Year(s)
ASP. Net, HTML		2017	9 Year(s)
JAVA SCRIPT		2017	9 Year(s)
SQL Server		2017	9 Year(s)
Visual Studio Dot Net, ADO .NET		2017	9 Year(s)
MS OFFICE		2019	1 Year(s)
Apex Data Loader, workbench, visualforce			2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
SALESFORCE		2021	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Bengali	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

US Work Status: Need H1 Visa

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time